projectwedding.com 2014-02-13

# Project Wedding

Updated:  July 25, 2013 

**PRIVACY POLICY**

WeddingWire, Inc. ("Company", "us" or "we") respects the privacy of the visitors to its projectwedding.com Web site (the "Site"). This Privacy Policy is intended to inform you of our policies and practices regarding the collection, use and disclosure of “Personal Information,” “Automatically Gathered Information" and "Anonymous Information" (each defined below) you submit to us or which we gather when you visit our Site. This Privacy Policy is hereby incorporated in our Terms of Use Agreement

This Privacy Policy applies to ALL users, including those just visiting this Site ("Users"). 

"Personal Information" is information about you that is personally identifiable to you, like your name, address, email address or phone number, as well as other non-public information that is associated with the foregoing. "Automatically Gathered Information" is information we collect as you visit our site. See "Automatically Gathered Information" below for more information. 

**CONSENT**

By using the Site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, and you expressly consent to the gathering and processing of your Personal Information by us or by third parties with whom we have a relationship, in accordance with the terms of this Policy. Your Personal Information may be processed by Project Wedding in the country where it was collected, as well as in other countries (including the United States) where laws regarding processing of Personal Information may be less stringent than the laws in your country. In addition, in the event you contact Project Wedding via telephone, you understand, acknowledge and agree that such phone conversations may be recorded. 

**NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES**

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time as our Services and Site change and expand. If we make material changes to this Policy, we may email announcements, introduce pop-up notifications, or otherwise notify you through other means. Unless otherwise provided, the revised terms will take effect when they are posted. Once any changes that we make to this Privacy Policy become effective, your continued use of the Site after such time will signify your acceptance of the new terms. 

**INFORMATION WE GATHER**   

**Registration**   
If you register with the Site, we may collect and store Personal Information that specifically identifies you or the account you set up with Us (your "Account"), including but not limited to information submitted by you during the registration process as well as your User ID and password. You agree that you will be responsible for maintaining your password as confidential and for any activity that occurs on your Account as a result of you sharing your password with another or failing to protect it. Project Wedding is not responsible for any loss or damage arising from your failure to maintain the confidentiality of your password. 

**User-Submitted Information**   
Project Wedding reserves the right to retain any and all information submitted by Users through use of the Site, including but not limited to reviews, public profile (MyProfile) information, information submitted to surveys (created by us or any other third party), personal messages sent through the Site, content posted (or “pinned”) to Inspiration Boards, and posts to message boards or forums. We may supplement Personal Information you provide us with additional information purchased from third parties for marketing purposes. 

**Email to Friends Feature and Referral Program**   
Project Wedding lets you easily connect your Profiles to friends/affiliates via email. Project Wedding also offers the ability to send friends/affiliates emails to Project Wedding. If you choose to use these features, we will use your email address to copy you on the message or to send on the email your behalf, and you hereby grant permission for such use. 

**Automatically Gathered Information**   
When you visit our Site, Project Wedding automatically collects information including but not limited to: browser type, browser software version, IP address, location information, and other information that may personally identify you. We reserve the right to collect and manage this information at our discretion. We may use cookies, web beacons and other tracking technologies to conduct research and analytics, to maintain records of Users’ activities on our Site, to manage use of our Site and Site services (including third party services), to customize and improve your user experience, and as deemed necessary for additional Site management purposes. We can and will use IP addresses to identify a User when we, in our sole discretion, determine that it is necessary to enforce compliance with our Terms of Use, Privacy Policy, or to protect our service, Site, customers, vendors, or others. 

**HOW WE USE AND DISCLOSE INFORMATION**   

**Generally**   
We may use your information (including Personal Information and Automatically Gathered Information) for multiple purposes including, but not limited to, uses necessary to operate the Site, maintaining records of Site usage to optimize Site functionality, analyzing User trends and other data, tailoring your User experience, and contacting you via email and other means to inform you about updates to our Services and those of our marketing partners and providing you with information relating to e-commerce transactions that you conduct on the Site. 

**Advertising**   
We may send you email and other communications including information that we think may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving email communications related to the Site either when you register to become a Member or via the Preferences section of your Account settings. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information about your visits to this Site and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. In addition, Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on the Site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads based on the users visit to the Site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy on Google's website. 

**Co-Branded or Partnered Services**   
Project Wedding may enter into co-branding or partnering relationships with third-party Web sites and companies to provide products and Services to our Users or to such third parties' users. Project Wedding may share your Personal Information, including User ID and password, with certain co-branded third-party service or product providers as required to provide a specific product or service that you request from a co-branded page or co-branded site. 

If you join Project Wedding through a co-branded or partnered site (e.g. on a co-branded Registration page), it is Project Wedding's general policy not to share anything other than summarized or aggregated data with the partnered site. However, any Personal Information you provide to the co-branded Site may be stored and used by the co-branded partner according to its own privacy policy. Please take the time to review these third-party privacy policies. Project Wedding is not liable for any information you submit to co-branded partner Sites. 

**Project Wedding's Contractors**   
To the extent necessary to provide you with the Services on the Site, we may provide your Personal Information to third party contractors who work on behalf of or with Project Wedding to provide you with such Services, to help us communicate with you or to maintain the Site. However, these contractors do not have any independent right to share your Personal Information. 

**Legal Requests**   
Project Wedding cooperates with all law enforcement inquiries, as well as other third parties to enforce laws, such as: intellectual property rights, fraud, theft, harassment and other rights. We can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about you if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to (a) comply with relevant laws or to respond to subpoenas or warrants served on us; (b) protect or defend the rights or property of Project Wedding or third parties; or (c) assist in any investigation. 

**Acquisition**   
If our company or assets related to the Site are acquired by another company, that company will possess the Personal Information collected by us and it will assume the rights and obligations regarding your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy inures to the benefit of successors and assigns of Project Wedding. 

**Anonymous Information**   
"Anonymous Information" is information that is not associated with or linked to your Personal Information. Anonymous Information does not permit the identification of individual persons. We may create Anonymous Information records from Personal Information by excluding information (such as names) that makes the information personally identifiable to you. We may use this Anonymous Information to analyze inquiry, request and usage patterns so that we may enhance Services and the Site. We reserve the right to use and disclose Anonymous Information to third parties at our discretion. 

**SECURITY**   

We will use commercially reasonable methods to keep Personal Information securely in our files and systems. Please note that with current technology, we cannot guarantee the security of your data as it travels over the Internet. 

**THIS SITE CONTAINS LINKS TO OTHER SITES**   

Project Wedding is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of any other Web Sites to which the Site links or which link to the Site. We encourage you to read the posted privacy statement whenever interacting with any Web Site. 

**REGARDING CHILDREN**   

WeddingWire Sites are designed and intended for use by adults. We do not intentionally gather Personal Information about persons who are under the age of 18. 

**CONTACTING US**   

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices of this Site, you may contact Customer Service at [info@projectwedding.com](mailto:info@projectwedding.com)
